Guide to the BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 1)
BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 1)
- Series VII: Industry Code #33, Manufacturing
  - Code no.4063: Curtiss-Wright Corporation, Wright Aeronautical Division and International Union, United Automobile, Aircraft and Agricultural Implement Workers of America, Local 669, CIO, 1961-1974 (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Code no.4066: Douglas Aircraft Company, Inc. and International Union, United Automobile, Aerospace, and Agricultural Implement Workers of America, locals 148, 243, 1093, 1960-1974 (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - Code no.4080: Lockheed Aircraft Corporation and Aeronautical Industrial District Lodge 727 and The International Association of Machinists, 1960-1971 (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Code no.4081: Lockheed-Georgia Company and International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers, AFL-CIO, Locals, 1027, 709, 2260, 2386, 1971-1974 (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - Code no.4083: McDonnell Aircraft Corporation and International Association of Machinists, District 9, 1960-1972 (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - Code no.4084: North American Aviation, Inc. and International Union, United Automobile, Aerospace, and Agricultural Implement Workers of America, 1960-1975 (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - Code no.4091: International Harvester Company, Solar Division and International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers, Silvergate District Lodge 50, 1960-1975 (Box 21, Folder 9)
- Series VIII: Industry Code #42, Wholesale Trade
  - Code no.289: N/A and Bakery Drivers Local Union 276, 1970-1974 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Code no.289: N/A and Independent and French Bakery Drivers Unions 276 and 952, 1970-1974 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Code no.376-1: Delmarva Poultry Processors Association and Chauffeurs, Warehousemen and Helpers Local Union No. 876, 1968- 1971 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Code no.6404: Detroit Lumbermen's Association and Lumber Drivers, Warehousemen and Helpers, Local Union 458, 1964-1979 (Box 9, Folder 13)
- Series IX: Industry Code #44, Retail Trade
  - Code no.6700-1: The American Stores Company and Acme Markets, Inc. and Amalgamated Food Employees Union Local 72, 1960- 1968 (Box 22, Folder 1)
    - Item 1: The American Stores Company and Acme Markets, Inc. and Amalgamated Food Employees Union, AFL-CIO, Local 72, 1960-1962; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 22, Folder 1)
      Agreement effective 8/6/1960 and expires on 11/9/1962. Covers 1300 workers in Forty Fort, PA
      Format: Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA).
    - Item 2: The American Stores Company and Acme Markets, Inc. and Amalgamated Food Employees Union, AFL-CIO, Local 72, 1962-1965; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 22, Folder 1)
      Agreement effective 11/10/1962 and expires on 5/8/1965. Covers 1200 workers in Forty Fort, PA
    - Item 3: The American Stores Company and Acme Markets, Inc. and Amalgamated Food Employees Union, AFL-CIO, Local 72, 1965-1968; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 22, Folder 1)
      Agreement effective 5/8/1965 and expires on 5/3/1968. Covers 1200 workers in Forty Fort, PA
  - Code no.6704-1: Cleveland Food Industry Committee and Retail Store Employees Union, AFL-CIO, Local 880, 1959-1974 (Box 22, Folder 2)
    - Item 1: Cleveland Food Industry Committee and Retail Store Employees Union, Local 880, 1959-1961; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 22, Folder 2)
      Agreement effective 8/31/1959 and expires on 9/3/1961. Covers an unknown number of workers in Cleveland, OH
    - Item 2: Cleveland Food Industry Committee and Retail Store Employees Union, Local 880, 1961-1963; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 22, Folder 2)
      Agreement effective 9/4/1961 and expires on 9/1/1963. Covers 5725 workers in Cleveland, OH
    - Item 3: Cleveland Food Industry Committee and Retail Store Employees Union, Local 880, 1971-1974; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 22, Folder 2)
      Agreement effective 9/6/1971 and expires on 9/1/1974. Covers an unknown number of workers in Cleveland, OH
  - Code no.6704-2: Cleveland Food Industry Committee and Retail Store Employees Union, AFL-CIO, Local 880, 1963-1971 (Box 22, Folder 3)
    - Item 1: Cleveland Food Industry Committee and Retail Store Employees Union, Local 880, 1963-1965; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 22, Folder 3)
      Agreement effective 9/2/1963 and expires on 9/4/1965. Covers 5788 workers in Clevland, OH
    - Item 2: Cleveland Food Industry Committee and Retail Store Employees Union, Local 880, 1965-1968; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 22, Folder 3)
      Agreement effective 9/5/1965 and expires on 9/1/1968. Covers 5000 workers in Clevland, OH
    - Item 3: Cleveland Food Industry Committee and Retail Store Employees Union, Local 880, 1968-1971; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 22, Folder 3)
      Agreement effective 9/2/1968 and expires on 9/5/1971. Covers an unknown number of workers in Clevland, OH
  - Code no.6706-4: First National Stores, Inc. and Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen of North America, AFL-CIO, 1967- 1973 (Box 22, Folder 4)
    - Item 1: First National Stores, Inc. and Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen of North America, AFL-CIO, 1967-1971; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 22, Folder 4)
      Agreement effective 11/27/1967 and expires on 2/27/1971. Covers 2400 workers.
    - Item 2: First National Stores, Inc. and Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen of North America, AFL-CIO, 1971-1973; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 22, Folder 4)
      Agreement effective 2/28/1971 and expires on 3/3/1973. Covers 2400 workers.
  - Code no.6721: Great Atlantic and Pacific Tea Company and Retail Clerks International Association, AFL-CIO, Local 212, 1961- 1964 (Box 22, Folder 5)
    - Item 1: Great Atlantic and Pacific Tea Company and Retail Clerks International Association, AFL-CIO, Local 212, 1961-1962; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 22, Folder 5)
      Agreement effective 5/1/1961 and expires on 4/30/1962. Covers 1200 workers in Buffalo, NY
    - Item 2: Great Atlantic and Pacific Tea Company and Retail Clerks International Association, AFL-CIO, Local 212, 1962-1964; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 22, Folder 5)
      Agreement effective 5/1/1962 and expires on 4/30/1964. Covers 1200 workers in Buffalo, NY
  - Code no.6722: Great Atlantic and Pacific Tea Company and Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen of North America, AFL-CIO, Local 342, 1958-1968 (Box 22, Folder 6)
    - Item 1: Great Atlantic and Pacific Tea Company and Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen of North America, AFL-CIO, Local 342, 1958-1960; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 22, Folder 6)
      Agreement effective 5/28/1958 and expires on 5/29/1960. Covers 5000 workers in New York
    - Item 2: Great Atlantic and Pacific Tea Company and Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen of North America, AFL-CIO, 1962-1965; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 22, Folder 6)
      Agreement effective 6/4/1962 and expires on 7/31/1965. Covers an unknown number of workers in New York
    - Item 3: Great Atlantic and Pacific Tea Company and Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen of North America, AFL-CIO, Local 342, 1962-1964; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 22, Folder 6)
      Agreement effective 5/4/1962 and expires on 6/2/1964. Covers 2200 workers in New York
    - Item 4: Great Atlantic and Pacific Tea Company and Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen of North America, AFL-CIO, Local 342, 1965-1968; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 22, Folder 6)
      Agreement effective 8/1/1965 and expires on 8/3/1968. Covers 2200 workers in New York
  - Code no.6724: Great Atlantic and Pacific Tea Company and Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen of North America, AFL-CIO, Local 342, 1960-1968 (Box 22, Folder 7)
    - Item 1: Great Atlantic and Pacific Tea Company and Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen of North America, AFL-CIO, Local 342, 1960-1962; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 22, Folder 7)
      Agreement effective 5/30/1960 and expires on 6/2/1962. Covers 7500 workers in New York
    - Item 2: Great Atlantic and Pacific Tea Company and Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen of North America, AFL-CIO, Local 342, 1962-1964; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 22, Folder 7)
      Agreement effective 6/4/1962 and expires on 6/2/1964. Covers 6000 workers in New York
    - Item 3: Great Atlantic and Pacific Tea Company and Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen of North America, AFL-CIO, Local 342, 1965-1968; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 22, Folder 7)
      Agreement effective 8/1/1965 and expires on 8/3/1968. Covers 7500 workers in New York
    - Item 4: Great Atlantic and Pacific Tea Company and Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen of North America, AFL-CIO, Local 342, 1968-1971; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 22, Folder 7)
      Agreement effective 8/4/1968 and expires on 8/7/1971. Covers 5500 workers in New York
  - Code no.6725: Great Atlantic and Pacific Tea Company and Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen of North America, AFL-CIO, Locals 464, 174, 489, 1971-1977 (Box 22, Folder 8)
    - Item 1: Great Atlantic and Pacific Tea Company, Incorporated and Butchers, Food Handlers and Allied Workers Union, AFL-CIO, Local 174, 1971-1974; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 22, Folder 8)
      Agreement effective 1/1/1971 and expires on 8/10/1974. Covers an unknown number of workers in Bronx, NY
    - Item 2: Great Atlantic and Pacific Tea Company, Incorporated and Food Handlers Union, AFL-CIO, Local 489, 1974-1977; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 22, Folder 8)
      Agreement effective 8/11/1974 and expires on 8/13/1977. Covers 1400 workers in Kings Co., NY; Queens, NY; Bronx, NY; New York, NY; Nassau Co., NY; Suffolk Co., NY; Westchester, NY; Putnam Co., NY; Dutchess Co. NY
    - Item 3: Great Atlantic and Pacific Tea Company, Incorporated and BAmalgamated Meat Cutters and Food Store Employees Union, AFL-CIO, Local 464, 1974-1977; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 22, Folder 8)
      Agreement effective 8/17/1974 and expires on 8/13/1977. Covers an unknown number of workers in Paterson, NJ
    - Item 4: Great Atlantic and Pacific Tea Company, Incorporated and Butchers, Food Handlers and Allied Workers Union, AFL-CIO, Local 174, 1974-1977; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 22, Folder 8)
      Agreement effective 8/17/1974 and expires on 8/13/1977. Covers an unknown number of workers in Kings Co., NY; Queens, NY; Bronx, NY; New York, NY; Nassau Co., NY; Suffolk Co., NY; Westchester, NY; Putnam Co., NY; Dutchess Co. NY
  - Code no.6727: Great Atlantic and Pacific Tea Company and Retail Store Employees Union, Local 400, 1960-1962 (Box 22, Folder 9)
    - Item 1: Great Atlantic and Pacific Tea Co., Inc. and Retail Store Employees' Union, AFL-CIO, Local 400, 1960-1962; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 22, Folder 9)
      Agreement effective 1/31/1960 and expires on 3/3/1962. Covers an unknown number of workers in Washington, DC; Prince Georges Co., MD; Charles Co., MD; St. Marys Co., MD; Calvert Co., MD
  - Code no.6731: Grocery Stores and Retail Store Employees Union, Local 782, 1961-1963 (Box 22, Folder 10)
    - Item 1: Grocery Stores and Retail Stores Employees Union, AFL-CIO, Local 782, 1961-1963; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 22, Folder 10)
      Agreement effective 3/12/1961 and expires on 3/10/1963. Covers 2000 workers in Jackson Co., MO; Clay Co., MO; Platte Co., MO; Johnson Co., KS; Wyandotte Co., KS
  - Code no.6739: Meat Markets and Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen of North America, AFL-CIO, Local 546, 1959- 1970 (Box 22, Folder 11)
    - Item 1: Service Meat Markets and Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen of North America, AFL-CIO, Local 546, 1959-1961; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 22, Folder 11)
      Agreement effective 10/4/1959 and expires on 10/7/1961. Covers an unknown number of workers in Chicago, IL
    - Item 2: Service Meat Markets and Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen of North America, AFL-CIO, Local 546 Addendum, 1959-1961; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 22, Folder 11)
      Agreement effective 10/5/1959 and expires on 10/7/1961. Covers an unknown number of workers in Chicago, IL
    - Item 3: Service Meat Markets and Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen of North America, AFL-CIO, Local 546, 1961-1964; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 22, Folder 11)
      Agreement effective 10/8/1961 and expires on 10/3/1964. Covers an unknown number of workers in Chicago, IL
    - Item 4: Service Meat Markets and Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen of North America, AFL-CIO, Local 546 Addendum, 1961-1964; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 22, Folder 11)
      Agreement effective 10/7/1961 and expires on 10/3/1964. Covers an unknown number of workers in Chicago, IL
    - Item 5: Service Meat Markets and Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen of North America, AFL-CIO, Local 546, 1964-1967; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 22, Folder 11)
      Agreement effective 10/4/1964 and expires on 10/7/1967. Covers 2000 workers in Chicago, IL
    - Item 6: Service Meat Markets and Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen of North America, AFL-CIO, Local 546, 1967-1970; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 22, Folder 11)
      Agreement effective 10/8/1967 and expires on 10/3/1970. Covers an unknown number of workers in Chicago, IL
  - Code no.6740: Meat Markets and Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen of North America, AFL-CIO, Local 546, 1959- 1974 (Box 22, Folder 12)
    - Item 1: Self-Service Meat Markets and Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen of North America, AFL-CIO, Local 546, 1959-1961; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 22, Folder 12)
    - Item 2: Self-Service Meat Markets and Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen of North America, AFL-CIO, Local 546 Addendum, 1959-1961; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 22, Folder 12)
    - Item 3: Self-Service Meat Markets and Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen of North America, AFL-CIO, Local 546, 1961-1964; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 22, Folder 12)
    - Item 4: Self-Service Meat Markets and Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen of North America, AFL-CIO, Local 546 Addendum, 1961-1964; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 22, Folder 12)
    - Item 5: Self-Service Meat Markets and Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen of North America, AFL-CIO, Local 546, 1964-1967; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 22, Folder 12)
      Agreement effective 10/4/1964 and expires on 10/7/1967. Covers 2500 workers in Chicago, IL
    - Item 6: Self-Service Meat Markets and Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen of North America, AFL-CIO, Local 546, 1967-1970; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 22, Folder 12)
    - Item 7: Retail Meat Markets and Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen of North America, AFL-CIO, Local 546, 1970-1972; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 22, Folder 12)
      Agreement effective 10/4/1970 and expires on 9/30/1972. Covers 4000 workers in Chicago, IL
    - Item 8: Retail Meat Markets and Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen of North America, AFL-CIO, Local 546, 1972-1973; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 22, Folder 12)
      Agreement effective 10/1/1972 and expires on 10/29/1973. Covers 4000 workers in Chicago, IL
    - Item 9: Retail Meat Markets and Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen of North America, AFL-CIO, Local 546 Addendum, 1973-1974; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 22, Folder 12)
      Agreement effective 9/30/1973 and expires on 9/28/1974. Covers 4000 workers in Chicago, IL
  - Code no.6741: Retail Operators and Retail Clerks Union Local 1222, 1956-1969 (Box 22, Folder 13)
    - Item 1: Retail Operators and Retail Clerks Union, AFL-CIO, Local 1222, 1956-1959; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 22, Folder 13)
      Agreement effective 4/2/1956 and expires on 3/31/1959. Covers 2019 workers in San Diego Co., CA
    - Item 2: Retail Operators and Retail Clerks Union, AFL-CIO, Local 1222, 1959-1964; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 22, Folder 13)
      Agreement effective 4/1/1959 and expires on 3/31/1964. Covers an unknown number of workers in San Diego Co., CA
    - Item 3: Retail Operators and Retail Clerks Union, AFL-CIO, Local 1222, 1964-1969; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 22, Folder 13)
      Agreement effective 4/1/1964 and expires on 3/31/1969. Covers 2670 workers in San Diego Co., CA
  - Code no.6763: Food Employers Council, Inc.; Meat Dealers Association of So. California, Inc.; So. California Employers Council; Independent Retail Meat Operators and Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen of North America, AFL-CIO, 1964-1967 (Box 22, Folder 14)
    - Item 1: Retail Meat Industry and Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen of North America, AFL-CIO, Local 551, 1964-1967; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 22, Folder 14)
      Agreement effective 12/18/1964 and expires on 11/5/1967. Covers 2500 workers in Southern CA
  - Code no.6764: Food Employers Council, Inc.; Meat Dealers Association of So. Calif., Inc.; Associated Meat Jobbers; Independent Retail Meat Operators and Meat Cutters, AFL-CIO, Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen of North America, AFL-CIO, Local 439, 1964-1967 (Box 22, Folder 15)
    - Item 1: Retail Meat Industry and Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen of North America, AFL-CIO, Local 439, 1964-1967; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 22, Folder 15)
      Agreement effective 12/18/1964 and expires on 11/5/1967. Covers 2083 workers in Southern CA
  - Code no.6769: Retail Bakeries and Bakery and Confectionery Workers' International Union of America, Local 2, 1959-1968 (Box 22, Folder 16)
    1959-1961, 1965-1968
    - Item 1: Associated Retail Bakeries of Greater Chicago and Bakery and Confectionary Workers' International Union of America, Local 2, 1959-1961; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 22, Folder 16)
      Agreement effective 5/9/1959 and expires on 5/13/1961. Covers an unknown number of workers in Chicago, IL
    - Item 2: Associated Retail Bakeries of Greater Chicago and Bakery and Confectionary Workers' International Union of America, Local 2, 1961-1963; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 22, Folder 16)
      Agreement effective 5/13/1961 and expires on 5/1/1963. Covers 1000 workers in Chicago, IL
    - Item 3: Associated Retail Bakeries of Greater Chicago and Bakery and Confectionary Workers' International Union of America, Local 2, 1965-1968; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 22, Folder 16)
      Agreement effective 5/9/1965 and expires on 5/11/1968. Covers an unknown number of workers in Chicago, IL
  - Code no.6770: Akron-Canton, Ohio Area Stores and Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen of Northern America, Local 427, 1961- 1963 (Box 22, Folder 17)
    - Item 1: Akron-Canton, Ohio Area Stores and Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen of North America, AFL-CIO, Local 427, 1961-1963; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 22, Folder 17)
      Agreement effective 9/4/1961 and expires on 9/1/1963. Covers an unknown number of workers in Cuyahoga Co., OH; Lake Co., OH; Geauga Co., OH; Ashtabula Co., OH; Lorain Co., OH; Medina Co., OH; Erie Co., OH; Ashland Co., OH; Richland Co., OH; Huron Co., OH
  - Code no.6782: A&P Tea Company, and Milgram Food Stores, Inc. and Retail Store Employees Union Local 782, 1963- 1966 (Box 22, Folder 18)
    - Item 1: Great Atlantic and Pacific Tea Co. and Milgram Food Stores, Inc. and Retail Store Employees Union, AFL-CIO, Local 782, 1963-1966; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 22, Folder 18)
      Agreement effective 3/11/1963 and expires on 5/8/1966. Covers an unknown number of workers in Jackson Co., MO; Clay Co., MO; Platte Co., MO; Cass Co. MO; Johnson Co., KS; Wyandotte Co., KS
  - Code no.6785: Denver Retail Grocers and Retail Clerks International Association, AFL-CIO, Local 7, 1964-1967 (Box 22, Folder 19)
    - Item 1: Denver Retail Grocers and Retail Clerks International Association, AFL- CIO, Local 7, 1964-1967; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 22, Folder 19)
      Agreement effective 7/12/1964 and expires on 10/31/1967. Covers 3000 workers in Denver, CO
  - Code no.6786: Philadelphia Food Store Employers Labor Council and Warehouse Employees Union, Local 169, International Brotherhood of Teamsters, 1965-1977 (Box 23, Folder 1)
    - Item 1: Philadelphia Food Store Employers Labor Council and Warehouse Employees' Union, Local 169, 1965-1968; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 23, Folder 1)
      Agreement effective 7/4/1965 and expires on 7/6/1968. Covers 1950 workers in Philadelphia, PA
    - Item 2: Philadelphia Food Store Employers Labor Council and Warehouse Employees' Union, Local 169, 1968-1971; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 23, Folder 1)
      Agreement effective 7/7/1968 and expires on 7/3/1971. Covers 1953 workers in Philadelphia, PA
    - Item 3: Philadelphia Food Store Employers Labor Council and Warehouse Employees' Union, Local 169, 1971-1974; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 23, Folder 1)
      Agreement effective 7/4/1971 and expires on 7/13/1974. Covers 1800 workers in Philadelphia, PA
    - Item 4: Philadelphia Food Store Employers Labor Council and Warehouse Employees' Union, Local 169, 1974-1977; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 23, Folder 1)
      Agreement effective 7/14/1974 and expires on 1/29/1977. Covers an unknown number of workers in Philadelphia, PA
  - Code no.6787: United Supermarket Association of Michigan and Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen of North America, Local 539, 1964-1973 (Box 23, Folder 2)
    - Item 1: United Super Market Association of Michigan and Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen of North America, AFL-CIO, Local 539, 1964-1967; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 23, Folder 2)
      Agreement effective 3/28/1964 and expires on 4/1/1967. Covers an unknown number of workers in Michigan
    - Item 2: Independent Super Market Operators and Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen of North America, AFL-CIO, Local 539, 1967-1970; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 23, Folder 2)
      Agreement effective 4/2/1967 and expires on 8/2/1970. Covers 1200 workers in Michigan
    - Item 3: No employer specified and Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen of North America, AFL-CIO, Local 539, 1970-1973; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 23, Folder 2)
      Agreement effective 8/3/1970 and expires on 8/4/1973. Covers 5000 workers in Michigan
  - Code no.6788: Food Retailers Association of the Greater New York Trading Area and Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen of North America, Local 342, 1970-1973 (Box 23, Folder 3)
    - Item 1: Greater New York Food Employers' Labor Relations Council and Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen of North America, AFL-CIO, Local 342, 1970-1972; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 23, Folder 3)
      Agreement effective 2/9/1970 and expires on 6/24/1972. Covers 6000 workers in Richmond Co., NY; Kings Co., NY; Queens Co., NY; Nassau Co., NY; Suffolk Co., NY
    - Item 2: Food Retailers Association of the Greater New York Trading Area and Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Retail Food Stores Employees Union, AFL-CIO, Local 342, 1972-1973; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 23, Folder 3)